

Hello, My name is YUNUSA ISAH CHIROMA

MEDICAL STUDENT, ENTREPRENEUR.

PROFILE...

With more than 5 years of experience as a graphic designer in different multinational companies I have also worked as IT Partner and CTO of a Invictus Mentalia, I am an individual who is motivated, experienced, intelligent, full of skills, and ready to work hard to help my company's business targets.

CONTACT

- +234-70-4614-6747
- □ chiroma@crators.app
- Abuja, Nigeria.
- www.heischiroma.com
- in Linkedin/in/heischiroma

SKILLS

Graphic Design

Team Building

Leadership and Agile Learning

Effective communication

Creative Direction

.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CHIEF MARKETING OFFICER

AA Horizons Acad

2020 - present

- Directed more than 15 art projects related to the company's marketing interests
- Define standard graphic design templates with the team for the company
- Work closely with the marketing team regarding social media trends to increase traffic

GRAPHIC DESIGNER & CTO

SYROL Technologies

2016 - 2020

- Designing social media posts based on corporate graphic design templates (41% increase in traffic)
- Work closely with the marketing team to design graphic designs based on social media trends

EDUCATION HISTORY

GIWO SCIENCE ACADEMY

High School

2013 - 2016

- Graduated as science student and the overall graduating student
- Best JAMB student with all Distinctions in WAEC and a single B

AHMADU BELLO UNIVERSITY, ZARIA.

MBBS

2016 - 2022

- Academic Excellence in Visual Communication, English, and Medicine
- Leader of the Student Association of the ABU SRC representing the college of Medicine.